<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="app_name">DroidTracker</string>

	<string name="trackers_list_title">List of Trackers</string>
	<string name="no_trackers">No one!</string>
	<string name="all_trackers_label">All Contacts with Permission</string>
	<string name="tracking_only_label">People Currently Tracking You</string>
	<string name="new_tracker_menu">Add Tracker</string>
	<string name="remove_tracker_menu">Remove Permission</string>
	<string name="stop_tracking_menu">Stop All Tracking</string>
	<string name="settings_menu">Preferences</string>
	<string name="about_menu">About/Help</string>


	<string name="stop_tracking_dialog_body">Stop Current Tracking?</string>

	<string name="idle_tracker_dialog_title">Actions for </string>
	<string name="idle_tracker_dialog_title_default_tracker_name">this tracker</string>
	<string name="idle_twitter_tracker_dialog_title">Publish on Twitter</string>

	<string name="ok_button_label">Ok</string>
	<string name="cancel_button_label">Cancel</string>

	<string name="tracking_request_msg_title">Tracking Request</string>
	<string name="tracking_request_msg_body">Accept Tracking Request from</string>
	<string name="tracking_request_msg_button_accept">Accept</string>
	<string name="tracking_request_msg_button_refuse">Refuse</string>

	<string name="prompt_providers_settings_msg_title">DroidTracker Message</string>
	<string name="prompt_providers_settings_msg_body">To use DroidTracker, you must first turn on a
		location source in Settings. Go to settings and turn it on now?
	</string>

	<string name="prompt_providers_settings_one_source_msg_title">DroidTracker Message</string>
	<string name="prompt_providers_settings_one_source_msg_body">DroidTracker will provide better
		location information if all location providers are activated. There is
		currently only one provider activated. Do you want to activate more
		now?</string>
	<string name="prompt_providers_settings_one_source_ok_button">Ok</string>
	<string name="prompt_providers_settings_one_source_no_need_button">Not now</string>

	<string name="tracking_confirmation_text">Send my location to </string>
	<string name="tracking_period">Sending Period (in minutes):</string>
	<string name="confirm_tracking">Start Sending</string>
	<string name="cancel_tracking">Cancel</string>

	<string name="invalid_period_dialog_title">Invalid Period!</string>
	<string name="invalid_period_dialog_message">The tracking period must be set to a round
		number of minutes.\nYour tracking request has been cancelled.</string>

	<string name="result_prefix">Here is my last known location:\n\n</string>
	<string name="result_source">Source:</string>
	<string name="result_when">\nDate:</string>
	<string name="result_where">\n\n</string>
	<string name="result_geocode">\n</string>
	<string name="result_map_url">\n\nMap URL:\n</string>

	<string name="twitter_msg_header">I'm here: </string>

	<string name="tracking_refused_msg">Sorry but your tracking request has been
		refused.</string>

	<string name="preferences_sms_category_label">SMS Preferences</string>

	<string name="preferences_sms_start_passphrase_label">Configure Start Pass Phrase</string>
	<string name="preferences_sms_start_passphrase_summary">Sets the sentence that triggers tracking when
		received by SMS from an allowed contact.</string>
	<string name="preferences_sms_start_passphrase_default">Where are you?</string>

	<string name="preferences_sms_stop_passphrase_label">Configure Stop Pass Phrase</string>
	<string name="preferences_sms_stop_passphrase_summary">Sets the sentence that stops tracking when
		received by SMS from a tracking contact.</string>
	<string name="preferences_sms_stop_passphrase_default">Stop</string>

	<string name="preferences_sms_period_passphrase_label">Configure Period Pass Phrase</string>
	<string name="preferences_sms_period_passphrase_summary">Sets the sentence that defines the tracking
		period (if any) when contained in a tracking trigger message.</string>
	<string name="preferences_sms_period_passphrase_default">Every {x} minutes</string>
	<string name="preferences_sms_period_passphrase_error_dialog_title">Invalid Pass Phrase!</string>
	<string name="preferences_sms_period_passphrase_error_dialog_msg">The period pass phrase must use the following
		format:\n \"some text {x} some text\"\nFor instance:\n \"Every {x}
		minutes\"</string>


	<string name="lostphone_mode_label">Lost/Stolen Phone Mode</string>
	<string name="lostphone_mode_summary">Configure Lost/Stolen phone mode
		activation and pass phrase.</string>
    <string name="lostphone_mode_activation_category_label">Activation</string>
	<string name="activate_lostphone_mode_label">Activate Lost/Stolen Mode</string>
	<string name="activate_lostphone_mode_summary">If checked, activate Lost/Stolen Phone Mode.
	</string>
	<string name="preferences_sms_lostphone_passphrase_label">Configure Pass Phrase</string>
	<string name="preferences_sms_lostphone_passphrase_summary">Sets the sentence that triggers tracking when
		received by SMS from any number without confirmation or notification.
	</string>
	<string name="preferences_sms_lostphone_passphrase_default">I want my phone back!</string>
	<string name="lostphone_mode_picture_category_label">Snapshots to Picasa</string>
    <string name="activate_snapshots_label">Activate Snapshots</string>
    <string name="activate_snapshots_summary">If checked, the phone will take a picture and upload it to the configured Picasa album when sending the location message.
    </string>
    <string name="picasa_login_label">Picasa Login</string>
    <string name="picasa_login_summary">Set your Picasa Login Name. </string>
    <string name="picasa_passwd_label">Picasa Password</string>
    <string name="picasa_passwd_summary">Set your Picasa Password. </string>
    <string name="picasa_album_label">Picasa Album</string>
    <string name="picasa_album_summary">Set the name of the Picasa album to upload to (will be created if doesn't exist). </string>

	<string name="tracking_confirmation_requested_label">Confirmation Needed</string>
	<string name="tracking_confirmation_requested_summary">If checked, ask for confirmation when receiving
		tracking request by SMS.</string>

	<string name="preferences_sending_category_label">Sending Preferences</string>
	<string name="preferences_display_info_when_sending_label">Notify When Sending Location</string>
	<string name="preferences_display_info_when_sending_summary">If checked, sends a notification with the sent
		message when sending.</string>

	<string name="preferences_display_settings_if_single_provider_label">Show Providers Settings If One is Missing
	</string>
	<string name="preferences_display_settings_if_single_provider_summary">If checked, prompt the user for location
		providers settings activation if not both providers (network and SMS)
		are activated, otherwize user will be prompted only when no provider
		is activated.</string>

	<string name="periodicity_label_every">Every</string>
	<string name="periodicity_label_minutes">minutes</string>

	<string name="tracker_periodicity_prefix">tracking every</string>
	<string name="tracker_periodicity_suffix">mn</string>

	<string name="about_label">About</string>
	<string name="about_version">DroidTracker v1.10</string>
	<string name="about_author">
		by Olivier Bonal\n
	</string>
	<string name="about_text">The aim of this application is to allow you
		sharing your location as a readable address using SMS. This means even
		your grandmother who has no computer and no smartphone but an old SMS
		capable mobile can know where you are! ;-)\nAny contact that you allow
		can send a request SMS to your phone containing some specific keywords
		that you define. When the phone receives the SMS, it will ask for your
		confirmation (if you set this as a preference) and then automatically
		start tracking your position and sending it back to the person who has
		requested it as a readable address (with a link to a Google Map
		centered on your location). This is done one time or periodically
		according to his/her choice (i.e. the keywords used in their
		SMS).\nYou can also trigger the sending yourself from the application
		to any of your allowed contacts. This lets you choose to send your
		position once or periodically and even include an option to send your
		position by mail or by Twitter (if Twidroid is installed).\nA
		lost/stolen phone mode now allows you configuring a secret start
		pass-phrase that will trigger a location sending with no confirmation
		request or notification even when sent by a non authorized contact
		which means it can be sent from any phone. This is usefull to find
		your phone back if it is lost or stolen. As with the standard start
		pass phrase, the location can be sent once or periodically (if the SMS
		also contains the period pass-phrase).\n\nWarning: As you probably
		guessed, this application can send a large number of SMS and should
		therefore be used carefully for people with no unlimited SMS plans.
	</string>
	<string name="about_footer">\n\nMost icons by Axialis Team:
		http://www.axialis.com/free/icons</string>

	<string name="help_label">Help</string>
	<string name="help_header">
		<b>DroidTracker Help</b>
		\n\n
	</string>
	<string name="help_text">
		<b>Welcome Screen</b>
		\nThe Welcome Screen of this application is the list of trackers, i.e
		of people from your phone contacts that you allow requesting and being
		sent your location. On first run, this list will be empty. To add a
		new tracker, use the \"Add Tracker\" menu to chose a new allowed
		tracker from your contacts or to create a new one.\nThe top spinner let you change the
		display to view only people currently tracking you. However, even in
		the default mode, people tracking you will be shown.\nWarning: When
		adding a new tracker, part of this contact\'s information is copied to
		the tracker\'s database. If the contact information changes (number
		changed, mail address added...), please make sure to update the
		tracker\'s data simply by pressing on the contact\'s name and choosing
		\"Refresh Contact Data\" from the menu.\n
		You can of course remove
		tracking permission from any of your contacts.
		This is done by simply
		pressing on the tracker\'s name in the tracker\'s list and then
		choosing
		the proper option in the contextual menu.\n\n
		<b>Start Tracking (initiated by the tracker)</b>
		\nThis is done using SMS. People who want to receive your location by
		SMS must send a request SMS (or let you initiate the tracking, cf next
		section). This SMS must contain a trigger \"start pass phrase\" that
		you
		can define yourself in the \"Preferences\" menu (default is \"Where
		are
		you?\"). An additional optional pass-phrase can be defined to
		request
		a tracking period. If this pass-phrase is present, then the
		location
		information will be sent periodically, the period being a
		number of
		minutes specified in the SMS with the period pass-phrase. The
		period
		pass-phrase is defined in the Preferences page (default is
		\"Every
		{x} minutes\").\nIf only the start pass-phrase is present in
		the SMS, the
		location information will be sent only once. If both are
		present, the
		information will be sent at the given period. The start
		pass-phrase
		must be contained in the SMS for any tracking to
		start.\nNote that
		pass-phrases are handled in a case insensitive
		way.\n\n
		<b>Start Tracking (initiated by yourself)</b>
		\nYou can decide to
		start sending your location yourself. This is done
		by simply pressing
		on the tracker\'s name in the tracker\'s list. This
		will prompt with a
		contextual menu for this tracker in which you will
		chose \"Start
		Sending Info\" (Note that this option will only be
		available if the
		selected
		contact is not already tracking you). This
		will lead you to a screen from
		which you can
		chose the tracking mode
		between \"Only Once by SMS\", \"Only Once by
		Mail\" or \"Periodically
		by SMS\"
		(which lets you specify the period as a round
		number of
		minutes). You
		can then start the sending or dismiss the
		dialog.\n\n
		<b>Stop Tracking (initiated by the tracker)</b>
		\nThis is again done by SMS. The tracker can stop a periodic tracking
		by
		sending you an SMS containing the stop pass-phrase. This stop
		pass-phrase can
		be defined in the application Preferences page (default
		is \"stop\").\n\n
		<b>Stop Tracking (initiated by yourself)</b>
		\nThis is done very easily by simply pressing on the tracker\'s name
		in
		the list of trackers. This will prompt you with a contextual menu
		in
		which you can chose the \"Stop Current Tracking\" option. Note that
		this
		option
		will only be available on trackers that are currently
		tracking you.
		If
		the selected contact is not currently tracking you,
		other contextual options will
		appear.
		\n\n
		<b>Confirmations and Notifications</b>
		\nThe application is asking you for confirmation every-time a tracking
		request SMS is received. It is also displaying a notification
		every-time your location is sent to someone. Both of these features
		can be disabled from the \"Preferences\" menu.
		\n\n
		<b>Lost/Stolen Phone Mode</b>
		\nA Lost Stolen Phone mode allows you defining a
		secret pass-phrase
		allowing you to receive your location from any
		phone without
		confirmation request or notification. You can
		activate/deactivate this
		mode and configure the associated pass-phrase
		from the application
		preferences page.\nSince version 1.10, a new feature is associated to the lost/stolen phode mode: the snapshot feature. It allows making the Android device take a picture when the reply message is sent to you and then publish it to a Picasa web album of your choice. This can help you finding where your phone really is. This feature can also be used for a completely different purpose: as a webcam which is SMS remote controlable, that can take pictures at given times and send them to Picasa.
		\n\n
		<b>Twitter Integration</b>
		\nWhen Twidroid (most popular Android Twitter client) is installed on
		your phone, Droidtracker interacts with it and adds Twitter on top of
		the list of allowed contacts. This allows you clicking on it to
		publish your current location to your Twitter page. As for sending
		your location by mail, publishing your location on twitter cannot be
		done periodically as it is requesting a sending confirmation from the
		user and therefore cannot be performed in the background.\n
		Click Here to Install Twidroid:\n
		http://market.android.com/search?q=pname:com.twidroid\n
	</string>

	<string name="faq_label">FAQ</string>
	<string name="faq_header">
		<b>Frequently Asked Questions</b>
		\n\n
	</string>
	<string name="faq_text">
		<b>Sometimes, the location sent is not very accurate, why?
		</b>
		\nThere are 2 locations providers: network and GPS.\nGPS is the
		accurate one but it uses satelites and needs a clear vision of the sky
		to work.\nNetwork locates you using the position of the GSM cells or
		WiFi Hot Spots that it detects near you so, depending where you are,
		it sometimes only gives a rough idea of the area where you are.
		Network however works even indoors. In the message that the tracker
		will receive, the source of the location (network or gps) will be
		shown.\n\n
		<b>Why does it sometimes take a couple of minutes between the
			request message is sent and the location is received?</b>
		\nAs explained in previous answer, there are 2 location providers. GPS
		is the more accurate but takes longer to provide a location than
		network. If GPS is available (or is off but auto activation is on),
		the application will wait a couple of minutes for a GPS location. If
		none is received during that time, it probably means you don\'t have a good enough GPS signal (indoor for instance) and the application will fall back to sending the network location. The couple of minutes delay is due to this but it allows the tracker to receive a more accurate location. \n\n
		<b>I cannot see Twitter in my Trackers List, what\'s wrong?</b>
		\nTwitter is only available in the list of Trackers if the Twidroid
		application is installed on your device. All you have to do to see it
		is then to dowload the Twidroid application from the market and
		configure it to use your twitter account.\nClick Here to Install Twidroid:\n http://market.android.com/search?q=pname:com.twidroid\n\n
		<b>Why has the auto-activating GPS feature disappeared? (I loved
			that one)</b>
		\nDue to a new Google policy, auto changing some settings in the
		background becomes impossible from Android version 1.5 (aka cupcake).
		From version 1.10 of DroidTracker, this feature is then replaced by a
		lighter one prompting the location providers settings page instead of
		changing them automatically.\n\n
	</string>
	<string name="mail_subject">My Current Position</string>
	<string name="chooser_title">Sending Position</string>
	<string name="location_unknown_msg">Could not determine location.</string>
	<string name="location_no_translation_msg">Could not translate current latitude and
		longitude to a readable address.</string>

	<string name="sent_notication_title_prefix">Location sent to</string>

</resources>
